Guide to the Frauke Heard-Bey and David Heard collection AD.MC.064
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Other GCC (Gulf Cooperation Council) countries, 1964-2011
  - Qatar, 1966-2005
    - State of Qatar. Ministry of Education. Report on Education Development, 1970-1971, presented to the XXXIII session of the International Conference on Education, Geneva, September 1971 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - State of Qatar. Ministry of Industry and Agriculture. Technical Note 39. Farm Enterprises and Resource Use in Qatar. A.K. Mitra and J.E. Flack. UN Development Program / FAO, November 1976 (Volume 114)
    - State of Qatar. Ministry of Finance and Petroleum. Department of Petroleum Affairs. Petroleum Concessions Agreements and Laws, 1973 (Volume 115)
      HD9576.Q2 P43 1973
    - State of Qatar, Secretariate [sic] of the Council of Ministers, Palace of Doha. Statement about the achievements of the government of the State of Qatar in internal fields. 1396 A.H. Doha, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Technical Note No. 42. Water resources and Agriculture in Qatar, by J.G. Pike and A.K. Mitra (FAO). (typescript text, 16 pp.), December 1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - The 1977 (AH 1397) State Budget (mimeograph text, unattributed, 7 pages (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1964-2002
    - Ad-Dir'iyyah. [Map/guide], undated, circa 2000 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Al-dalil al-ahsa'il li-ta'alim al-fatah = Statistical guide for teaching girls. (Riyadh: Bureau of Statistics. Directorate of Public Teaching of Girls, 1388-89 A.H.), 1968-1969 (Volume 116)
    - Al-harman al-sharifan = The two holy places [booklet about the Hajj in Mekka]. Undated. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Al mamluka al-'arabiyah al-sa'udiyah fii murah al-sahafah al-'alamiyah = The Kingdom of Saudi Arabia in the mirror of the world press. (Riyadh: Ministry of Information), 1385 A.H. / 1967 A.D. (Volume 117)
    - Altayebat International City for Sciences and Knowledge [brochure], Jeddah. (undated) (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Aramco 1966. [prospectus/annual report] (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Aramco World. A Peninsula in Profile. (special reprint of article from Nov.-Dec. 1964 issue) (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Aramco World magazine, January-February 1982 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - al-Dalīl al-iḥṣāʼī = Statistical Handbook, 1387-1388 A.H. / 1966-1967 A.D. (Ministry of Knowledge: Kingdom of Saudi Arabia)., 1967-1968 (Volume 118)
    - El Reinado de Arabia Saudita en fotos y figuras / Das Koenigreich von Saudi Arabien in Bildern und Zaehlen / Illustrazioni e cifre del Regno dell'Arabia Saudita (Riyadh: Ministry of Information), 1967 (Volume 119)
    - Emergent Nations: the magazine of rising peoples. Vol. 2, no. 2. [issue on Saudi Arabia], Summer 1966 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - 'Eshrun 'aman min injazat al-takhtiit al-tanwii = Twenty years of planning accomplishments. AH 1390-1410 / AD 1970-1989. (Riyadh: Ministry of Information) (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Faisal Speaks. (Riyadh: Ministry of Information], undated, circa 1969 (Volume 120)
      DS244 .F2 1966
    - Ghaith, Abdulhakim. The marching caravan: the story of modern Saudi Arabia. (Jeddah: Almadina Almonawara), 1967 (Volume 121)
      DS244.G5 1967
      BSN: 2599031
    - Gulfwire Supplement. Assessing Saudi Arabia's Current Policy on Foreign Investment, 22 November 2000 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Jeddah Tourist Map (Jeddah: Zaki Farsim), undated, circa 1995 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - King Abdulaziz Foundation for Research and Archives. [booklet outlining aims and activities of foundation, in English and Arabic], undated, circa 1999 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - King Abdulaziz Foundation for Research and Archives. [booklet outlining aims and activities of foundation, in English and Arabic], undated, circa 2000 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Kuwait, Gulf States, and Saudi Arabia. BOAC [brochure], 1970 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Le sante en arabie seoudite (Riyadh: Ministry of Information), undated, circa 1963 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Mejcher, Helmut. "Saudi Arabia's 'Vital Link to the West: Some political strategic and tribal aspects of the Transarabian Pipeline (TAP) in the stage of planning, 1942-1950. Middle Eastern Studies, Vol. 18, No. 4 [Reprint], October 1982 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Middle East Consultants, Ltd. (London): spiral bound prospectus with several forecast reports about Saudi Arabia and the region, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - National Geographic. "Saudi Arabia: Beyond the Sands of Mecca," by Thomas Abercrombie. Reprint from January 1966 issue. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Oil exhibit visitor's guide [brochure, unidentified publisher, perhaps Aramco headquarters], circa 1964 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Press cuttings, 1993, 2000-2002 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Press cuttings, 2004-2005 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Review of Arabian Petroleum and Economics. Vol. 2, No. 12 - Vol. 3, No. 1. Dec. 1966-Jan. 1967. Special issue on Saudi Arabia. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Salah, Said. Brief pictorial guide to Saudi Arabia. (Alkhobar: International Publication Agencies), undated, circa 1970s (Volume 122)
      DS203.S33
    - Sa'ud [folder, containing two booklets, and DVD, about life of King Sa'ud bin Abdul Aziz], undated, circa 2000s (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Saudi Arabian Monetary Agency. Address to H.M. King Faisal bin Abdul Aziz, on the presentation of the Eighth Annual Report of the Monetary Agency by its Governor, Mr. Anwar Ali, September 1969 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Schweitzer, Guenther. "Bevoelkerung, traditionelle Lebens- und Wirtschaftsformen." reprint of article that appeared in Saudi Arabien: Natur, Geschichte, Mensch und Wirtschaft (Tuebingen: Horst Erdmann Verlag,1976). Inscribed by author. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Tatweer, Issue 31, A.H. 1422. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - A visitor's guide to Dhahran. Arabian American Oil Company [brochure], 1966 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Periodicals and news digests, 1972-2015
  - News digest services: A.P.S. Diplomat and A.P.S. Review (Beirut / Nicosia: Arab Press Service), 1982-2002
    - APS Diplomat: Fate of the Arabian Peninsula, 1982-2002
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 3, nos. 1-6; Vol. 4, nos. 1-15, January - December 1982 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 5, Nos. 1-2, 4-12; Vol. 6, Nos. 1-11, January - December 1983 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula, Vol. 7, Nos. 1-9; Vol. 8, Nos. 1-9, January - December 1984 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 9, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 10, Nos. 1, 3-9, January - December 1985 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula, Vol. 11 No.s 1-6; Vol. 12, Nos. 2-6, January - December 1986 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 13, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 14, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1987 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula, Vol. 15, Nos. 1, 3-6; Vol. 16, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1988 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula, Vol. 17, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 18, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1989 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 19, Nos. 1, 3-6; Vol. 20, Nos. 1-2, 4-5, January - December 1990 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 21, Nos. 1-2, 4-6; Vol. 22, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 23, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 24, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1992 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 25, Nos. 1-2, 4-6; Vol. 26, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 27, Nos. 1-4; Vol. 28, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1994 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 29, Nos. 1-6, Vol. 30, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1995 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 31, Nos. 1-5; Vol. 32, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1996 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 33, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 34, No. 2, January - August 1997 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula: Vol. 38, Nos. 5-6, November - December 1999 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula, Vol. 39, nos. 1-4; Vol. 40, Nos. 1-2, January - April, July-August 2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula, Vol. 41, Nos. 5-6; Vol. 42, Nos. 1-5, May - November 2001 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Fate of the Arabian Peninsula, Vol. 43, Nos. 2-6; Vol. 44, No. 2, February - August 2002 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - APS Diplomat: News Service, 1982-2002
      - News Service: Vol. 16, Nos. 1-25; Vol. 17, Nos. 1-25, January - December 1982 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - News Service: Vol. 18, Nos. 1-2, 4-26; Vol. 19, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1983 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - News Service, Vol. 20, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 21, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - News Service: Vol. 22, Nos. 1-25; Vol. 23, Nos. 1-7, 9-26, January - December 1985 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - News Service: Vol. 24, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 25, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1986 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - News Service: Vol. 26, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 27, Nos. 1-10, 12-26, January - December 1987 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - News Service, Vol. 28 No 1, 3-26; Vol. 29, Nos. 1, 3-26, January - December 1988 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - News Service, Vol. 30, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 31, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1989 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - News Service: Vol. 32, Nos. 1-26 (with gaps); Vol. 33, Nos. 1-26 (with gaps), January - December 1990 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - News Service: Vol. 34, Nos. 1-8, 10-24; Vol. 35, Nos. 1-2, 4-26, January - December 1991 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - News Service, Vol. 36, No. 1-26 (with gaps), index; Vol. 37, 1-26, index, January - December 1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - News Service: Vol. 38, Nos. 1-26 (with gaps); Vol. 39, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - News Service, Vol. 40, Nos. 1-18, 20-21; Vol. 41, Nos. 2-26, January - December 1994 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - News Service, Vol. 42, Nos. 1-26, index; Vol. 43, 1-26, index, January - December 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - News Service, Vol. 44, Nos. 1-26, index; Vol. 45, Nos. 1-26, index, January - December 1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - News Service, Vol. 46, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 47, Nos. 4-6, January - August 1997 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - News Service, Vol. 51, Nos. 21-26, November - December 1999 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - News Service, Vol. 52 nos. 1-26; Vol. 53, Nos. 1-7, January - August 2000 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - News Service, Vol. 54, Nos. 17 - 26; Vol. 55, Nos. 1-26 (with gaps), April - December 2001 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - News Service, Vol. 56 Nos. 3-26; Vol. 57, Nos. 1-11, January - September 2002 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - APS Diplomat: Operations in Oil Diplomacy
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 3, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 4, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1982 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 5, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 6, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 7, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 8, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 9, Nos. 1-7; Vol. 10, Nos. 1-5, 7-15, January - December 1985 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 11, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 12, Nos. 1-4, 6-7, January - December 1986 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 13, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 14, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1987 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 15, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 16, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1988 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 17, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 18, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1989 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 19, Nos. 1, 3-6; Vol. 20, Nos. 1-2, 4, 6, January - December 1990 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 21, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 22, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1991 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 23, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 24, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1992 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 25, Nos. 2, 4-6; Vol. 26, Nos. 1-6, February - December 1993 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 27, Nos. 1-5; Vol. 28, Nos. 2-6, January - December 1994 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 29, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 30, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1995 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 31, Nos. 2-6; Vol. 32, Nos. 1-6, February - December 1996 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 33, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 34, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1997 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 38, nos. 5-6, November - December 1999 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 39, nos. 1-3, 5-6; Vol. 40, Nos. 1-2, January - August 2000 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 41, Nos. 5-6, May - June 2001 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Operations in Oil Diplomacy, Vol. 43, Nos. 1, 3 - 6; Vol. 44, No. 3, January - September 2002 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - APS Diplomat: Recorder, 1982-2002
      - Recorder, Vol. 16, Nos. 2-26, January - June 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Recorder, Vol. 17, Nos. 1-25c, July - December 1982 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Recorder, Vol. 18, Nos. 4 - 26, January - June 1983 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Recorder, Vol. 19, Nos. 3 - 26, July - December 1983 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Recorder, Vol. 20, Nos. 3 - 26, January - June 1984 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Recorder, Vol. 21, Nos. 3-26, July - December 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Recorder, Vol. 22, Nos. 1-26, January - June 1985 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Recorder, Vol. 23, Nos. 3 - 7, 9 - 26, July - December 1985 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Recorder, Vol. 24, Nos. 2-26B, January - June 1986 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Recorder, Vol. 25, Nos. 2, 4-26B, July - December 1986 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Recorder, Vol. 26, Nos. 1-26, January - June 1987 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Recorder, Vol. 27, Nos. 1-9, 11-26, July - December 1987 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Recorder, Vol. 28 Nos. 1-25, January - June 1988 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Recorder, Vol. 29 Nos. 1-25, July - December 1988 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Recorder, Vol. 30, Nos. 1-26, January - June 1989 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Recorder, Vol. 31, Nos. 1-14, 16-26, July - December 1989 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Recorder, Vol. 32, Nos. 1-2, 4-5, 7-17, 19-26, January - June 1990 (Volume 49, Folder 1)
      - Recorder, Vol. 33, Nos. 1-8, 11-17, 19-25, July - December 1990 (Volume 49, Folder 2)
      - Recorder, Vol. 34, Nos. 1-6, 8-22, 24-25, January - June 1991 (Volume 49, Folder 3)
      - Recorder, Vol. 35, Nos. 2-26, July - December 1991 (Volume 49, Folder 4)
      - Recorder, Vol. 36, Nos. 1-13, 15, 18-26, January - June 1992 (Volume 49, Folder 5)
      - Recorder, Vol. 37, Nos. 1-26, July - December 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Recorder, Vol. 38, Nos. 1-2, 4-10, 13-26, January - June 1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Recorder, Vol. 39, Nos. 1-26, July - December 1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Recorder, Vol. 40, Nos. 1-17, 19-20, January - June 1994 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Recorder, Vol. 41, Nos. 1-26, July - December 1994 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Recorder, Vol. 42, Nos. 1-5, 7-26, January - June 1995 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Recorder, Vol. 43, Nos. 1-26, July - December 1995 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Recorder, Vol. 44, Nos. 1-2, 4-21, 23-26, January - June 1996 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Recorder, Vol. 45, Nos. 1-26, July - December 1996 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Recorder, Vol. 46, Nos. 1-16, January - April 1997 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Recorder, Vol. 46, Nos. 17-26, April - June 1997 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Recorder, Vol. 47, Nos. 3, 5, July - August 1997 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Recorder, Vol. 51, Nos. 20-26B, November - December 1999 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Recorder, Vol. 52 nos. 1-13, 16-17, 20, 23-26, January - June 2000 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Recorder, Vol. 53, Nos. 1-5, July - August 2000 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Recorder, Vol. 54, Nos. 17-26, April - June 2001 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Recorder, Vol. 55, Nos. 1-14, July - September 2001 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Recorder, Vol. 55, Nos. 15-17, 19-22, 24, October - December 2001 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Recorder, Vol. 56 No. 1-2, 4-14, January - April 2002 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Recorder, Vol. 56, Nos. 15-26, April - June 2002 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Recorder, Vol. 57, Nos. 5 - 9, July - August 2002 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - APS Diplomat: Re-drawing the Islamic Map
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 3, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 4, Nos. 1-12, January - December 1982 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 5, Nos. 1-7; Vol. 6, Nos. 1-5, January - December 1983 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 7, Nos. 1-5; Vol. 8, Nos. 2-6, January - December 1984 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 9, Nos. 1, 3-6; Vol. 10, Nos. 1, 3-7, January - December 1985 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 11, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 12, Nos. 1-5, January - November 1986 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 13, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 14, Nos. 1-2, 4-6, January - December 1987 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 15, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 16, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1988 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Re-Drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 17, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 18, Nos. 1-6, January - June 1989 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Re-Drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 19, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 20, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1990 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 21, Nos. 1-2, 4-6; Vol. 22, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1991 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 23, Nos. 1-3; Vol. 24, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1992 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 25, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 26, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1993 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 27, Nos. 1-5; Vol. 28, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1994 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 29, Nos. 1, 3-6; Vol. 30, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1995 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 31, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 32, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1996 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Re-drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 33, Nos. 1-4, 6, January - June 1997 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Re-Drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 38, no. 6, December 1999 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Re-Drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 39, Nos. 1-5; Vol. 40, No. 1, January - July 2000 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Re-Drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 41, Nos. 5-6; Vol. 42 No. 1-4, 6, May - December 2001 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Re-Drawing the Islamic Map, Vol. 43, No. 1-6; Vol. 44, Nos. 2-3, January - September 2002 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - APS Diplomat: Strategic Balance in the Middle East
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 3, Nos. 1-16; Vol. 4, Nos. 1-19, January - December 1982 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 5, Nos. 1-10; Vol. 7, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1983 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 7, Nos. 1-8; Vol. 8, Nos. 1-7, January - December 1984 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 9, Nos. 1-8; Vol. 10, Nos. 2-6, January - December 1985 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 11, Nos. 1-7; Vol. 12, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1986 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 13, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 14, Nos. 1-7, January - December 1987 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 15, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 16, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1988 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 17, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 18, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1989 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 19, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 20, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1990 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 21, Nos. 1-2, 4-6; Vol. 22, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1991 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 23, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 24, Nos. 1-2, 4-6, January - December 1992 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 25, Nos. 1-5; Vol. 26, Nos. 2-6, January - December 1993 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 27, Nos. 1-5; Vol. 28, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1994 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 29, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 30, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1995 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 31, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 32, Nos. 1-6, January - December 1996 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 33, Nos. 1-6, January - June 1997 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 38, No. 6; Vol. 39, 1-4, 6; Vol. 40, No. 1, December 1999 - July 2000 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 41, Nos. 4-6; Vol. 42, Nos. 1-6, April - December 2001 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Strategic Balance in the Middle East, Vol. 43, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 44, Nos. 1-2, January - August 2002 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - APS Review: Downstream Trends
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 20, Nos. 1-2, 4-26; Vol. 21, Nos. 1-5, 7-15, 17-25, January - December 1983 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 22, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 23, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1984 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 24, Nos. 1-25; Vol. 25, Nos. 1-7, 9-10, 12-26, January - December 1985 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 26, Nos. 1-25; Vol. 27, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1986 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 28, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 29, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1987 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 30, Nos. 1-26; Vols. 31, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1988 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 32, Nos. 5-26; Vol. 33, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1989 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 34, Nos. 1-4, 6-7, 9-26; Vol. 35, Nos. 1-10, 13-19, 21-22, 24-26, January - December 1990 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 36, Nos. 108, 10-25; Vol. 37, Nos. 1-2, 4-12, 14-26, January - December 1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 38, Nos. 1-14, 16, 19-26; Vol. 39, No. 1-26, January - December 1992 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 40, Nos. 1-3, 5-11, 14-22, 24-26; Vol. 41, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1993 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 42, Nos. 1-21; Vol. 43, Nos. 2-26, January - December 1994 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 44, Nos. 1-7, 9-26; Vol. 45, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1995 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 46, No. 1-4, 6-23, 25-26; Vol. 47, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1996 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 48, Nos. 1-8, 10-16, 19-26, January - June 1997 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 53, Nos. 21, 23-24, 26, November - December 1999 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 54, Nos. 1-19, 22, 25-26, Vol. 55, Nos. 1-7, January - August 2000 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 56, Nos. 17-26; Vol. 57, Nos. 1-19, 21-24, 26, April - December 2001 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Downstream Trends, Vol. 58, Nos. 3-4, 6-14, 16-26; Vol. 59, Nos. 1-2, 7-11, January - September 2002 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - APS Review: Gas Market Trends
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 20, Nos.1-2, 4-26; Vol. 21, Nos.1-26, January - December 1983 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 22, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 23, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1984 (Box 58, Folder 1)